Bernie, I made a mess!
(Dr Hofstadter:)I'm terribly sorry
that I upset your mother.
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's all right.
She'll forgive you.
(Sheldon:)She has to or
she goes to hell.
(Dr Hofstadter:)I can't help but notice
(Dr Hofstadter:)how her unconditional
love for you
(Dr Hofstadter:)is diametrically opposed
to my own parenting strategies.
(Sheldon:)Well, you doled
out affection
(Sheldon:)as a reward for
achievement--
(Sheldon:)a proven way to
raise a child.
(Sheldon:)Or train a rat.
(Dr Hofstadter:)But look how well
you turned out.
(Sheldon:)I'd feign modesty at this point,
but who would believe me?
(Sheldon:)Still, you need
to consider
(Sheldon:)how successful Leonard's
brother and sister are.
(Dr Hofstadter:)I suppose.
(Sheldon:)While my brother and sister
are mouth-breathing idiots.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Do you suppose
you would've flourished more
(Dr Hofstadter:)in a reward-based environment?